http://www.predatorridge.com/privacy-policy/

MORE
MENU
HomeReal EstateReal EstateProperty SearchVirtual Home ToursShowhomesThe CommonageThe TipsCommunityEventsWinterActivitiesActivitiesBikingCyclingFitness ClassesFitness CentreGolfGolf SimulatorsHikingPickleballSkatingSkiingSnowshoeingTennisWine TastingYogaGolfGolfPredator CourseRidge CourseBook a Tee TimeGolf DealsLessons & ClinicsMembershipThe ShopAccommodationsAccommodationsPredator Ridge LodgeVacation Home RentalsLong Term RentalsAmenitiesSpecialsAirport Shuttle and Wine ToursLoyalty ProgramDiningDiningRange Lounge & GrillPallino'sCommonage MarketDelivery & Take-Out OrdersMenusWine ClubCOVID-19WeddingsWeddingsCeremony & Reception VenuesWedding PromotionsWedding StoriesCOVID-19Corporate EventsCorporate Events & MeetingsMeetingsGolf TournamentsHockey Canada Log CabinGroup Christmas PartiesBanquet FacilityCOVID-19Pet FriendlyCommunityAccommodationsAbout PRThe ExperienceWeatherThe RegionPartnersAwardsContact UsBlogVideosWebcamShopMembers LoginHomeowners LoginPRCEMC
Home / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Predator Ridge Limited Partnership uses and protects any information that you provide when you make a reservation, complete a guest registration form, sign-up on our website, or any other circumstance in which we may ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified. By providing information, you are consenting to being sent information about Predator Ridge.
The information we collect is used to better understand our visitors and to ultimately provide better service. We may use the information you provide to improve our products & services, for marketing purposes and/or for market research.
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Your information remains confidential and is gathered for the sole use of Predator Ridge Limited Partnership and its related companies. We will provide you with the opportunity to confirm and update your information by contacting us. Additionally, you will always have the opportunity to discontinue your consent for contact at any time.
At Predator Ridge Limited Partnership we stress the importance of privacy and are committed to earning the trust of our community and guests by adopting high standards for the protection of personal information.
Our policy outlines the type of personal information we collect and receive, the circumstances in which we collect or receive personal information, the policies and procedures we have established outlining its use and storage, and for sharing certain types of personal information in certain limited circumstances, the procedures you should follow if you have any questions or requests in respect of your personal information or our policies and procedures and the person to whom such questions or requests should be directed, and the means by which to communicate with that person.
In this policy ‘Predator Ridge Resort’ means Predator Ridge Limited Partnership and its affiliated companies. The words 'we' and 'Predator Ridge Resort’ do not include third parties involved in the delivery of services, however we have requested such third party suppliers to abide by the terms of our Privacy Protection Policy.
In this policy, personal information means information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available and is not part of your work identification.
It also includes information on guest preferences and usage, when such information is supplied to or recorded by Predator Ridge Resort in the course of transacting business with an individual or through contractual arrangements.
HOW YOU MAY PROVIDE US YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
By making a reservation or by using Predator Ridge Resort services.
By purchasing a home or property in the Predator Ridge community.
By providing it to us in communications regarding service delivery such as comment cards.
By providing the information to us by participating in a marketing initiative.
By visiting our website.
Below we will outline the type of information normally collected in each of these circumstances, the reasons for doing so, how we will use it and store it.
MAKING A RESERVATION When making a reservation or using Predator Ridge Resort services it is necessary to have information in order to identify you, contact you and to process your purchase and requests. This information usually includes your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number and expiration date, and language preference. It may also include, if you choose to share that information with us, your preferences regarding the delivery of your service such as type of room, type of bed, and the like. We also offer special discounts from time to time that may have qualifying criteria. Sometimes we offer special offers to, for example, seniors or for children. To assess your eligibility and process your reservation correctly, we need to record your date of birth at the time of booking. You may be required to provide personal identification with your date of birth in order to verify this upon check-in. From time to time, we offer packages or other services that involve third parties. If you are partaking of such a package or service, your personal information will be shared with that third party to the extent necessary to provide that service and process the purchase or request. Predator Ridge Resort may use the information you provide to send you offers and information about Predator Ridge Resort services and those of select third parties. Your information will not be given to these third parties but rather the offer of the third party will be provided to Predator Ridge Resort which will manage the distribution. If you do not wish to receive such offers and information you may unsubscribe or opt-out by sending an email to PredatorRidge@predatorridge.com, using the subject line "Unsubscribe", so indicating your request with sufficient personal identifiers so we can appropriately act on your request. All our marketing communication of this type will also contain instructions for unsubscribing.
INFORMATION PROVIDED TO US IN COMMUNICATIONS REGARDING SERVICE DELIVERY SUCH AS COMMENT CARDS Information provided to us in such a fashion will be used solely for the purpose of recording your comments, communicating with you in respect of them, reviewing them with the subject hotel and hotel personnel, for the purposes of recognizing employees for excellence of service delivery and for developing improvements in service delivery.
PREDATOR RIDGE RESORT OFFERS YOU THE ABILITY TO RECEIVE TARGETED, TIMELY NOTIFICATION OF TIME SENSITIVE OFFERS To sign up for this service we require you to provide us with your e-mail address, first name, last name, language preference, and city of residence. You may unsubscribe at any time using the link provided on every email message and you will no longer receive email offers and promotions for the specified subscription or website, as the case may be. You may at any time in the future opt-in to receive e-mail offers.
BY VISITING ONE OF OUR WEBSITES We use "cookies" on our websites. Cookies are pieces of information that an Internet site transfers to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them almost everywhere on the Internet. Predator Ridge Resort uses cookies to recognize visitors when they return to our sites. Once we know it's you, we can customize your online visit. We may also evaluate our content and services and tailor our websites, for visitors, based on other information we collect, such as IP addresses, which are numbers assigned to your computer whenever you use the Internet, pixel tags (or clear gifs), and the type of Internet browser or operating system you are using. This information is collected in the aggregate, but we may tie it to your personal information through cookie use as described above.
We use Google Analytics to measure how visitors interact with content on our websites. We also use Facebook Custom Audiences to ask Facebook to show you ads that are customized based on your interaction with our websites or our Facebook applications and to measure how you interact with those ads. All of these services use cookies and similar technologies, such as web beacons, tags and embedded scripts, to record information about your interaction with our websites. Additional information on how these services use such technologies can be found on Google’s website and Facebook’s website. The Google Analytics security and privacy principles summarize how Google protects information collected through Google Analytics. Facebook’s Data Use Policy describes how Facebook protects information collected through Facebook Custom Audiences.
If you do not wish to have data relating to your visits to our websites collected through Google Analytics, you may opt-out by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. You may also opt-out of Facebook Custom Audiences by visiting Facebook’s opt-out page.
WHY WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
To establish and maintain a responsible commercial relationship with you and to provide ongoing service.
To understand your needs and preferences. We maintain a record of the products and services you receive from us and we may ask for additional information so that we can serve you better. For example, we may record your preference for type of room.
To develop, enhance, market or provide products and services. For example, we look at our guests' use of our services so that we can better understand how to improve our services.
To manage and develop our business and operations.For example we analyze guest patterns of usage of our hotels and services to help us manage them efficiently and plan for future growth.
To meet legal and regulatory requirements.
WHEN DO WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION We disclose personal information only in these limited circumstances:
We may disclose a guest's personal information to a person who, in the reasonable judgment of Predator Ridge Resort, is seeking the information as an agent of the guest - for example, a travel agent who is booking a reservation on behalf of the guest.
Personal information will be shared with a third party involved in supplying the guest with the services they have purchased to the extent necessary to effect the supply and the processing of the transaction.
Personal information may be shared with a third party retained by Predator Ridge Resort to perform functions on its behalf such as reservations handling, data processing or storage, guest surveys or research.
Personal information may be shared with an agent retained by Predator Ridge Resort to evaluate a customer's credit worthiness or in order to collect a customer's account.
Personal information may be shared with a public authority or an agent of public authority if in the reasonable judgment of Predator Ridge Resort it appears that there is an imminent danger to life or property which could be avoided or minimized by disclosure of the information, or which disclosure is compelled by legal authority.
Any such disclosure of a guest's personal information by Predator Ridge Resort to a third party will be made only on a confidential basis conditioned upon the information being used only for the purpose for which it has been disclosed.
PRINCIPLES
Predator Ridge Resort will not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any other purpose than those identified above, except with your consent.
Predator Ridge Resort will protect your personal information with appropriate security safeguards.
Predator Ridge Resort will take appropriate steps to protect the confidentiality of your personal information when dealing with third parties.
Predator Ridge Resort will strive to keep your personal information as accurate and up to date as is necessary for the purposes identified above.
Predator Ridge Resort will honour your request to access your personal information in as timely fashion as is reasonably possible.
You are always free to refuse to provide personal information to us.You may also withdraw your consent with respect to the use of your personal information for marketing purposes at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice, by emailing us at predatorridge@predatorridge.com, using 'Unsubscribe' as the subject line, and providing us sufficient personal identifiers so we can act effectively on your request.
However, in either case, this may limit our ability to serve you.
If you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices or wish to make a request in respect of your personal information please contact our General Manager at info@predatorridge.com or if you prefer by writing us at: Predator Ridge Limited Partnership 100 Mashie Crescent Vernon, BC V1H 1V8
Order Your Free Predator Ridge Guide
Learn More
